<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects  on Ayush Mehrotra</title>
    <link>https://code-ayu.github.io/PortFolio/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects  on Ayush Mehrotra</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://code-ayu.github.io/PortFolio/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Mutual Funds Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://code-ayu.github.io/PortFolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://code-ayu.github.io/PortFolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>Nevertheless, as be harangued them, the satisfaction and admiration unanimously excited by his costume were dissipated by his words; and when he reached that untoward conclusion: “As soon as his illustrious eminence, the cardinal, arrives, we will begin,” his voice was drowned in a thunder of hooting.
“Begin instantly! The mystery! the mystery immediately!” shrieked the people. And above all the voices, that of Johannes de Molendino was audible, piercing the uproar like the fife’s derisive serenade: “Commence instantly!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Dog Breed Classifier </title>
      <link>https://code-ayu.github.io/PortFolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://code-ayu.github.io/PortFolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the dog breed classifier project. This project uses Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs). Given an image of a dog, our algorithm will identify an estimate of the canine’s breed. If supplied an image of a human, the code will identify the resembling dog breed. I have to design an algorithm in such a way that a given image should be identified as a dogs breed if it’s of a dog or tell a resembling dog breed if image is of a human .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
